Here is a picture from the introduction when you first encountered localization.
これは 最初にローカライゼーションを説明したときの概要の絵です
We have a map with all these landmarks in a global coordinate system,
マップにはグローバル座標系にこのようなすべての
observations from the on-board censor and the local coordinates system,
ランドマークがあり オンボードセンサーからの観測 局所座標系の
and we also have the information how the car moves between two timesteps.
2 つのタイムステップ間で車がどのように動くかについての情報を持ちます
Formally, the observations are defined as a vector z which includes
形式的には、観測値は、タイムステップ
all observations from timestep one to t. The observations could be range measurements,
1 から t までのすべての観測値を含むベクター z として定義されます 観察は
bearing angles, or images, for example.
例えば、距離測定値、方位角、または画像であり得ます
We also have the controls of the car as a vector u which includes
また車の制御をベクトル u として　これには
all control elements from timestep one to t. Typically,
タイムステップ1から t までのすべての制御要素が含まれます
you have low pitch or roll rates and velocity information.
通常 ローピッチまたはロールレート と速度情報があります
Finally, we have the map.
それからマップがあります
The map could be a grid map of the global environment,
マップはグローバルな環境のグリッドマップか、
or a database which includes global feature points and the lane geometry.
グローバルな特徴ポイントと車線の形状を含むデータベースです
Here, we do not add the time index t to the map
ここでは時間のインデックス t をマップに追加しません
because we assume the map does not change over time,
マップは時間経過によって変わることはなく
and we assume these variables are known.
これらの変数はわかっているとみなすからです
Again, what we want to estimate is the transformation between
推定するのは 車の局所座標系と
the local coordinate system of the car and the global coordinate system of the map.
マップのグローバル座標系の間の変換です
If we know this transformation,
この変換がわかると
then we also know the posts of the car in the global map.
グローバルマップでの車の位置もわかります
The position of the car at time t is defined with x.
時間 t のときの車の位置は x で定義します
If we assume we have a 2D map for example,
たとえば 2D マップがあった場合 x には x 座標と y 座標
x includes a position with x and y coordinates and also the orientation phi.
向き φ を持つ位置が含まれます
And these values are unknown.
これらの値は不明です
We will never know the state xt with perfect accuracy.
状態 xt を完全に正確に知ることはできません
What we want is to form a sufficiently accurate belief of the state xt,
必要なのは 状態 xt について十分に正確な信念を持つことであり
and we want to formulate this belief in a probabilistic way.
この信念を確率的な方法で公式化することです
Now here's a good question: Could you write down the posterior for the belief xt?
ここでちょうどよい質問があります"確証 xt の事後確率を書けますか?"